Guide to the Donald E. Knuth papers SC0097
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Addenda, 2011-200, Accession ARCH 2011-200
  - Selected papers
    - FG42: Long and Skinny Knight's Tours 29p (Box 2, Folder 1)
      handwritten MS; marked proofs
    - FG43: Leaper Graphs P147 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - FG44: Number Representations and Dragon Curves P37 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      index to files re dragon curves; tests of illustrations; marked proofs, before and after major changes
    - FG45: Mathematics and Art: The Dragon Curve in Ceramic Tile P59 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      tests of illustrations; marked proofs
    - FG46: Christmas Cards 34p (Box 2, Folder 5)
      samples of proof pages and other tests as I was writing this chapter
    - FG47: Geek Art 48p (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - FG49: An Earthshaking Announcement Q227 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      handwritten MS, test illustrations, marked proofs, correspondence
    - FG50: index (Box 2, Folder 8)
      ideas for the index (noted while writing the material); first draft pages
    - FG51: early copy of many chapters, used to index them (Box 2, Folder 9)
      (before the final order of chapters was decided, and before many of the chapters were written) [I brought these with me to work on in odd moments, during a long trip East]
    - FG52: first copy of the entire book, sent to proofreading team (Box 2, Folder 10)
      (and also used to index several chapters)
    - FG53: feedback from the proofreaders (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - CP00: miscellaneous notes and trial pages saved while making the CPbook (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - CP01: rough transcriptions of the taped luncheon conversations between Dikran Karagueuzian and Don Knuth in 1996 (these became Chapters 7--17) (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - CP02: first working copy of the entire CPbook as sent to proofreaders (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - CP03: extensive files of correspondence relating to all nine volumes of the series (Box 2, Folder 15)
      a few of these are from the 1990s, but the vast majority are from the period 2004--2011
  - The Art of Computer Programming
    Volume 4A of The Art of Computer Programming was published in January 2011; it represents the culmination of a project that Knuth had begun to write in 1973, when the first edition of Volume 3 was completed. More precisely, Volume 4A represents the "first part of the culmination" of this project, because it's only the first part of a "Volume 4", Combinatorial Algorithms.
    Table of contents of Volume 4A:
    7. Introduction to combinatorial searching
    7.1. Zeros and ones
    7.1.1. Boolean basics
    7.1.2. Boolean evaluation
    7.1.3. Bitwise tricks and techniques
    7.1.4. Binary decision diagrams
    7.2. Generating all possibilities
    7.2.1. Generating basic combinatorial patterns
    7.2.1.1. Generating all $n$-tuples
    7.2.1.2. Generating all permutations
    7.2.1.3. Generating all combinations
    7.2.1.4. Generating all partitions
    7.2.1.5. Generating all set partitions
    7.2.1.6. Generating all treesv
    7.2.1.7. History and further references
    Biographical/Historical note
    Background notes from Knuth:
    I began to collect material already in 1962, but began to work on Volume 4 in earnest in 1973, while visiting the University of Oslo on leave of absence from Stanford. For many years I made scribbled notes and continued to follow the literature as new techniques were discovered. However, I also took time out for other projects (notably typography) and other books (notably Concrete Mathematics and 3:16); then I spent a few years bringing Volumes 1--3 up to date in the 1990s. During 1999 I prepared "Volume 1 Fascicle 1", a paperback booklet about the MMIX computer; MMIX is a new computer intended for use in Volume 4 as well as in future editions of Volumes 1, 2, and 3. (All archives for that fascicle are included in the "MMIX archives" that were donated to Stanford in 2001, except that I recently found a few additional page proofs that I've included here.)
    I began to write the final copy of Volume 4A in the spring of 2001, in longhand as usual. My diary shows that I began to enter it into the computer on 22 July 2001: "happiness as I resume typing Volume 4 for the first time since 1977". (I had spent four months at the beginning of 1977 preparing what I thought would be Section 7.1; it was an 83-page typewritten manuscript, plus 22 pages of answers to exercises. About 100 copies were made and circulated at that time to interested computer scientists in various universities. The original of that MS is included below. Fate was, however, to intervene, because 1977 was the year that I realized I should drop everything else and work "temporarily" on typography. The TeX project began in the spring of that year and ran for roughly ten years.)
    In 2001 I actually began to work on Section 7.2.1.1, because I wasn't ready yet to write the opening parts of Chapter 7 (and Volume 4). I needed to flesh out the "middle" of the volume first, so that I'd have a better idea of what tone ought to be set in the opening pages. I continued with the next subsections, 7.2.1.2 through 7.2.1.7, which took several years because they cover a substantial amount of material. These drafts were first made available online as "prefascicles", beginning with prefascicle 2A --- which first went on the Web at 1am on 17 September 2001 [a few days after a somewhat more memorable event in the history of the USA]. Prefascicle 2B went online just before midnight on 31 December of that year.
    In 2002 I posted prefascicle 2C at noon on 13 June, and began to work on prefascicle 2d. Those two were however subsequently renamed 3A and 3B; prefascicle 3B went online on 14 February 2004. The prefascicles became true "fascicles", printed in paperback by Addison-Wesley, in 2005 when Volume 4 Fascicle 2 and (later) Volume 4 Fascicle 3 were ready.
    The same pattern was repeated as I continued to write: Prefascicles 4A and 4B went online in 2005, then Volume 4 Fascicle 4 was published in 2006. After finishing Section 7.2.1.7 I was ready to turn to the opening pages of the book; well, not quite: I began now with Section 7.1, still postponing the actual introductory pages. On 27 May 2005 I reread my draft of 7.1 from 1977 and made vague plans for reorganizing it substantially. By 30 May I had typed seven pages into the computer, and had accumulated a long list of things to look up in the library. (This was incidentally before Volume 4 Fascicle 3 was sent to the publisher in June of 2005.) I finished the first draft of Section 7.1.1 on 7 September 2005, and put it online as prefascicle 1B.
    However, I was soon to learn that Section 7.1.1 should be followed by hundreds of pages of new material, because Sections 7.1.2 and 7.1.3 were growing like crazy. Fascicle 2 had already been published, but at least two fascicles' worth of copy would be needed to precede it! So I decided to create a Fascicle 0, to precede Fascicle 1; and prefascicle 1B was renamed prefascicle 0B. I finished Section 7.1.2 (prefascicle 0C) on 17 March 2006. [Incidentally I had undergone surgery for prostate cancer at the end of 2005, and had radiation therapy during the spring of 2006.] By the end of 2006 I was ready to release Section 7.1.3, aka prefascicle 1A.
    I turned to the introductory material, prefascicle 0A, at the beginning of 2007, trying to be careful to make it "match" the end of Volume 3 without too much of a change in style even though the end of Volume 3 had been written some 35 years earlier. That prefascicle went public on 28 April 2007; Volume 4 Fascicle 0 was printed in paperback at the beginning of 2008.
    The remaining piece of the puzzle was Section 7.1.4, which turned out to be extremely interesting material for which I needed to do extensive research. I had typed two sample exercises destined for prefascicle 1B into my home computer on 30 June 2007, and had finished the first three pages by 2 July, thinking that the whole section would amount to roughly 30 pages max. In fact, Section 7.1.4 wound up 80 pages long, with 267 exercises(!), plus almost 60 pages more for answers to those exercises; and I didn't finish prefascicle 1B until 8 September 2008. Addison-Wesley published Volume 4 Fascicle 1 in 2009.
    The paperback fascicles went through several reprintings, and hundreds of readers sent comments. Much of this material had never before been published in book form, and in fact about a hundred of the exercises are original material that had never appeared before in any form. Therefore it was important to get extensive feedback from readers, and in this I was extremely fortunate. Finally at the end of 2010 I combined all the material from Fascicles 0, 1, 2, 3, and 4 of Volume 4, added some appendices, and sent the completed manuscript to Addison-Wesley's production department (in the form of PostScript files) on 3 December 2010 --- curiously on the very same day that I submitted the final PostScript files for another just-completed book, Selected Papers on Fun and Games, to CSLI's production department at Stanford.
    - Original typewritten manuscript of the opening pages of Volume 4 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      [This MS was incidentally typed on a "historic" early IBM Selectric Typewriter, which is now in the collection of the Computer History Museum.]
    - Changes to my working copy of Volume 1 Fascicle 1 (MMIX), Apr 2000- Jun 2002 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Section 7.2.1.1, the first hardcopy proofs of all pages, 1-Aug-2001 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Section 7.2.1.1, page proofs to make the index of prefascicle 2A, 4-Aug-2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Section 7.2.1.2, the first complete page proofs, 8-Dec-2001 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Changes to my working copies of prefascicles 2A&2B, summer 2001 - summer 2002 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Sections 7.2.1.1 and 7.2.1.2, drafts, after November 2002 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Section 7.2.1.3, proof copy used to make index, 11-Jun-2002 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Section 7.2.1.3, first copy (with subsequent corrections), 13-Jun-2002 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Section 7.2.1.3, version (with subsequent corrections), 29-Aug-2003 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Section 7.2.1.4, drafts, 2001 Nov-2003 Nov (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Sections 7.2.1.4 and 7.2.1.5, 10-Jan-2004 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Sections 7.2.1.4 and 7.2.1.5 (now called prefascicle 3B), 12-Jun-2004 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Section 7.2.1.6, early drafts, Apr 2004 -- Jul 2004 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Section 7.2.1.7, my first printed copy, 12-Oct-2004 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Section 7.2.1.7 as marked by Robin Wilson, given to me, early 2005 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - First draft of special copy for the paperback Fascicle 3, 13-Jun-2005 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Sections 7.1.1 and 7.1.2, early drafts, May 2005 -- Mar 2006 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Section 7.1.3, early drafts, Dec 2006-Oct 2008 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Section 7 (introduction to whole chapter, early draft), 2007 Apr (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Robin Wilson's comments on Section 7, 26-Jul-2007 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Section 7.1.4, early drafts, Oct 2007-Nov 2008 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous notes and pages saved while writing Volume 4A, 2001-2010 (Box 3, Folder 23)
      often shows tests of illustrations, or samples of computer program output, or sketches of ideas that didn't go into the main manuscript
- Addenda, 2014-128 (Teaching material), 1969-1989; Accession ARCH-2014-128
  - Course materials
    - Computer Science 144 Course Materials Master Compilation, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Computer Science 144A Course Materials Winter 1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Computer Sciecne 144B Course Materials Spring 1975 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Computer Science 150 Course Materials Master Compilation, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Computer Sicence 155 Course Materials Master Compilation, 1971-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Computer Science 155 Course Materials Master Compilation, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Computer Science 255 Course Materials Master Compilation, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Computer Science 155 Course Materials Master Compilation, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Computer Science 155 Course Materials Master Compilation, 1982-1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Computer Science 204 Course Materials Master Compilation, 1975-1979 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Handouts
    - Computer Sicence 279 Spring '84 Profs. Chuck Bigelow, Donald Knuth & Richard Southall Handouts, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Computer Sicence 204 Winter 85' Handouts, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Computer Science 260 Autumn '86 Handouts, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Computer Science 204 Autumn 82' Handouts, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Computer Science 304 Winter '87 Handouts, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Computer Science 349 Spring 87' Handouts, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Computer Science 209 Autumn 87' Handouts, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Computer Science 260 Autumn 88' Handouts, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Computer Science 304, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Computer Science 260 Autumn 89' Handouts, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Examinations
    - Computer Science 144 Examinations Master Compilation, 1969-1977 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Computer Science 155 Examinations Master Compilation, 1971-1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Computer Science 255 Examinations Master Compilation, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Computer Science 150 Examinations Master Compilation, 1974-1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Computer Science 144A Examinations Winter 1977 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Computer Science 360 Examinnations Winter 1988 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Addenda, 2016-104 (The Art of Computer Programming), Accession ARCH-2016-104
  - Volume 1 MSS, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Volume 2 MSS, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Volume 3 MSS, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Misc. notes (references, first analysis of algorithm, list of "complete names"), 1963-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Errata and addenda for publisher, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Computer programs written while preparing the manuscripts (mostly volume 2), undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Volume 4A MSS drafts, 2012 Feb 2 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Volume 4A MSS drafts, 2012 Apr 21 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Volume 4A MSS drafts, 2012 May 16 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Volume 4A MSS drafts, 2013 Jan 10 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Volume 4A MSS drafts, 2014 Feb 10 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Volume 4A MSS drafts, 2014 Dec 18 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Volume 4A MSS drafts, 2015 Apr 7 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Volume 4A MSS drafts (first draft of index), 2015 Apr 15 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Volume 4A MSS drafts (first draft of index), 2015 Apr 22 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Addenda, 2017-128, Accession ARCH-2017-128
  - Japan by Jill Carter Knuth, 1996 (Box 1)
- Websites, 2017-2018; Series 4
- Addenda, 2018-123, Accession ARCH-2018-123
  - Fantasia Apocalyptica Program, 2018
- Email, 1999-2019; Accession ARCH-2019-070
  Email in accession 2019-070 were captured from Knuth's Gmail and rmail accounts with ePADD software, resulting in over 32,000 messages. This series is comprised of: 11,834 incoming messages and 20,184 outgoing; 2,630 attachments (1,288 images, 865 documents, and 477 other); 7,394 correspondents; and several thousand extracted entities, including 5,348 names and 717 places.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access condition: Access to digital content is restricted to the Special Collections Reading Room. In order to access this content, please contact specialcollections@stanford.edu.
  The Donald Knuth papers include some messages identified by the donor, or Stanford Libraries, as sensitive. Access to these messages has been restricted according to federal and state guidelines, and Stanford Libraries policy, for up to 80 years from the date of message creation. These email messages are not included in this release of the collection; they will be made available between January 2045 through January 2099.
- Addenda, 2022-026, Accession ARCH-2022-026
  - Journal from Djursholm by Jill Knuth, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Northern Spring paste-ups, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Hooray, We're Going to America!: The Migration of the H.H. Bohning Family from Barkhausen, Hanover, to Cleveland, Ohio, in 1843 Edited and published by Jill Knuth, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Addenda, 2022-104
  - CS Tex Knuth, 29647; 1; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - CS Tex Knuth, 29640; 2; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Sonderkolloquium, All Questions Answered, Pr. Donald E. Knuth Stanford, 37021; 3; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - CNN "Future Watch" ind puzzler interviews, 33984; 4; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - UoM, Nomination as Honorary Doctors: Don Knuth, Christos Papadimitriou (in a European video format), 37804; 5; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - ITiCSE2003-invited Speakers. Christos Papadimitrious. Don Knuth. (European video format), 2003 July 1-2; 6; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - "Watch Your Language" by Scott Kim, 7; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - "Experiments with Digital Halftones" (unedited) Don Knuth, Speaker. College of Engineering-Michigan Engineering Television Network., 31923; 8; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - TCSE (illegible) 200 Tape I 4:15 Comp Science, 37593; 9; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Untitled, 10; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Corporate Technical Colloquium, R. R. Donnelley and Sons Co. Inc. "Can Computers Help Produce Beautiful Books?" Dr. Donald E. Knuth, 32286; 11; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Donald E. Knuth "Computer Musings: The Associative Law, or The Anatomy of Roatations in Binary Trees", 34303; 12; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - "An Anthology of Algorithm Animations using Zeus" by Marc H. Brown, 33480; 13; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - TEX 82 Knuth Session 11 Dub of Master, 30162; 14; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - TEX 82 Knuth Session 1 Dub of Master, 30160; 15; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - CS TEX Knuth, 29649; 16; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - Presedential Ceremony, 29234; 17; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - CS TEX Knuth Done KR Sess. #213, 29648; 18; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - CS TEX Knuth #413, 29650; 19; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - TEX 82 Knuth Session 10 Dub of master, 30162; 20; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - TEX 82 Knuth Session 12 Dub of master, 30162; 21; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 1)
  - MICRO TEX Technical Processing System: Includes a spiral bound textbook, two booklets, and a case of software floppydisks., 1985; 1; floppy disk(s) (5.25 inch) (Box 2)
  - Presedential Ceremony Honooring the 1979 Medal of Science Awardees, White House Ceremony, 29234; 2; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 2)
  - God and Computers, Introduction: Donald E. Knuth, 36439; 3; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - God and Computers "Randomization and Religion" Donald E. Knuth, 36446; 4; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - God and Computers "Language and Translation" Donald E. Knuth, 36460; 5; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - God and Computers "Aesthetics" Donald E. Knuth, 36467; 6; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - God and Computers, 36481; 7; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - God and Computers "Glimpses of God" Donald E. Knuth, 36495; 8; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - God and Computers "God and Computer Science" Donald E. Knuth, 36502; 9; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Don Knuth Computer Musings, 35yrs of Linear Probing, 35732; 10; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Don Knuth Computer Musings, 35yrs of Linear Probing, 35732; 11; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Don Knuth Computer Musings, 36095; 12; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Don Knuth Computer Musings, The MMIX architecture simulation, 36222; 13; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Don Knuth Computer Musings Fast input/output with multiple disks, 35815; 15; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Computer Musings W/O# 4080 [illegible note], 36578; 16; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Computer Musings W/O# 5113 [illegible note], 36676; 17; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Computer Musings-Knuth "Trees, Forests, and Polynominoes", 36865; 18; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Don Knuth Computer Musings, W/O# 7104, Trees ad alphabetic [illegible], 36132; 19; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - Don Knuth Lectures Christmas Tree Lecture, 35767; 20; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 2)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH session 12 1/1, 30162; 1; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 3)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH session 1 1/1, 30160; 2; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 3)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH session 2 1/1, 30160; 3; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 3)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH session 3 1/1, 30160; 4; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 3)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH session 4 1/1, 30160; 5; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 3)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH session 5 1/1, 30161; 6; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 3)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH session 6 1/1, 30161; 7; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 3)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH session 7 1/1, 30161; 8; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 3)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH session 8 1/1, 30161; 9; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 3)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH session 9 1/1, 30162; 10; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 3)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH session 10 1/1, 30162; 11; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 3)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH session 11 1/1, 30162; 12; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 3)
  - C.S. TEX Knuth 1 of 1 #5 [illegible], 29651; 1; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 4)
  - C.S. TEX Knuth 1 of 1 #4B, 29650; 2; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 4)
  - C.S. TEX Knuth 1/1 #3B, 29649; 3; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 4)
  - C.S. TEX Knuth 1/1 #2B, 29648; 4; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 4)
  - C.S. TEX Knuth 1/1 #1B w/o 4215, 29647; 5; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 4)
  - C.S. TEX KNUTH 1/1 #15A, 29644; 6; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 4)
  - C.S. TEX Knuth 1/1 #1A, 29640; 7; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 4)
  - CS 144C Knuth 18 1/1 Back-Up, 29353; 8; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 4)
  - C.S. TEX Knuth 1 of 1 wo 4215, 29643; 9; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 4)
  - CS TEX Knuth 1/1 #2A w/o 4215, 29641; 10; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 4)
  - C.S. Tex KNUTH #3A 1 of 1 w/o 4215, 29642; 11; videotape(s) (u-matic) (Box 4)
  - Brown Corpus--Version I. Epoch 480 Magnetic Reel Tape. BYU Humanities Research Center, 1; computer tape(s) (Box 5)
  - LOB Corpus---Tagged Horizontal. Epoch 480 Magnetic Reel Tape. BYU Humanities Research Center, 2; computer tape(s) (Box 5)
  - MELBOURNE SURREY CORPUS TEXT, 3; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - DON KNUTH Q+A, 57 ANNES [illegible], 1999; 4; audiocassette(s) (Box 5)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH Session 6 Dub of master, 30161; 5; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - CS TEX Knuth #4A, 29643; 6; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH Session 9 Dub of master, 30162; 7; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH Session 2, 30160; 8; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH Session 8, 30161; 9; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - CS TEX KNUTH #5B, 29651; 10; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH Session 4, 30160; 11; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - CS TEX Knuth #2A, 29641; 12; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - CS TEX Knuth #5A, 29644; 13; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH Session 5, 30161; 14; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - CS 144C Knuth, 29359; 15; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - TEX 82 KNUTH Session 3 Dub of master, 30160; 16; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)
  - TEX 82 Session 7, 30161; 17; videotape(s) (vhs) (Box 5)